47 minutes and we still haven't got our
food
because we're in latestage capitalism.
Spaghetti used to be a simple dish until
men made it about private equity and
imported goods. Then when you tack on
the fact that the man cuts costs by
underpaying women who make up 70% of all
servers, it's no wonder they have to
rely on tips. The patriarchy has done
irreversible damage. This is boring.
Let's go somewhere and do something. We
are doing something. We're on a date.
>> Well, it's boring. It's always like this
when I let you plan things.
>> Okay, hear me out.
>> No, you don't even know what I was going
to say.
>> You want to go fight monsters?
>> Trixie, Twilight is howling at the moon
again.
>> The great and powerful Trixie ain't
dealing with this no more. I'm taking
her to the vet.
>> My This is serious. I've seen symptoms
like this before, and it can only mean
one thing. I fear. Our dear friend
Twilight has been bitten by the pony
version of a werewolf. That's
impossible. I never got bit by a
werewolf.
Wait a minute.
But that's impossible. We would know if
Scootaloo was a werewolf, wouldn't we?
Not really. Squirtle is already so anim
animalistic and savage that even
werewolves pale in comparison.
>> There may be a cure. In the My Little
Pony version of Italy, there is a
mansion with a library and all things
werewolf. Maybe that can save your ass.
>> Girls, cancel everything. I have urgent
business in My Little Pony Italy.
Can I get like five tickets to the My
Little Pony version of Italy and a bag
of honey roasted peanuts?
>> Yo, [__] Two tickets to Germany and
all the beef jerky you got.
My name is Twilight Sparkle. I have come
to the My Little Pony version of Italy
with my closest friends and Fluttershy.
In search of a way to reverse the
metamorphosis of becoming a were pony
which is a werewolf but like a pony
version after being bitten by scuttaloo.
Our quest has brought us here to this
strange mansion in the woods which is
home to a mare that just may be able to
save my life. Also Rarity is here too
because she's inheriting a taco stand
for some reason.
>> Vibe check 67. 67.
>> What? God damn it.
>> Haha. Now you got to buy the rest of us
meatball subs when we get back to
Ponyville.
>> Twilight, when you die, can I have your
house tree?
>> I don't have rabies, Pinky. I am simply
undergoing a lyanthropic metamorphosis.
>> Now remember why we are here, every
pony.
>> The werewolf disease.
>> What? Oh no, darling. I was talking
about that taco stand I'm inheriting.
>> Oh my god, Rarity. No one gives a [__]
about your free taco cart. You won't be
saying that when I have a taco cart.
>> Before you bimos forget why we're really
here helping my wife, I would like to
remind you all that here in the My
Little Pony version of Italy, vampire
ponies run rampant and a single bite can
turn you into a nasty blood sucker. And
what do they suck? Perhaps poop out of
my ass.
Oh [__] vampires. Every pony run for
your lives.
Welcome, Miss Sparkle. Welcome. I
received word that you would be arriving
soon.
>> Yo, hold up. This [__] looks like a
vampire.
>> I am Sky Wishes. Please come inside
before you freeze solid. It is ever so
difficult to peel frozen ponies from the
steps.
>> Can we pee outside?
>> No, please use the restroom.
Princess Celestia lets me go poo poo
outside without my dias. I hate the
Italians. That's large in part due to
the fact that she finds forcing little
ponies to crap outside to be
humiliating. So it gives her a power
trip.
>> Yeah, you're the only one who likes it.
Pinky pie. The rest of us hate it
because Ponyville Ricks of piss and
[__]
>> Hey now, don't go speaking for the rest
of us like that, my yellow friend.
She said she really wants to see your
library. Haha. She's a bit of a nerd.
Now she says she hopes your library
contains research on werewolf
stabilization. We don't have anything
like that in Ponyville because our
libraries are exclusively full of
picture books about friendship. Yes, it
is very unequipped for the dangers of
the real world.
>> Do you have anything for the blood
cancer known as leukemia?
Pinky, we're we're kind of doing
Twilight's Medical Emergency right now.
>> Our archives are really quite extensive.
I'm sure you'll find it just at the end
of the hall in the library. Yay! I love
books. And while you do that, I shall
show Miss Trixie to the room you'll be
staying in. The rest of you background
ponies shall remain here.
>> Hey yo, did that [__] just call us
background ponies?
Hey [__] is the moon always red here?
>> If the moon appears red for you, it's
the sign that a vampire is near. You
must be careful here in Italy as
vampires roam freely in this land.
>> The great and powerful Trixie fears no
vampire because she eats a [__] ton of
garlic.
You You're a vampire.
>> They could be anywhere. And they do love
to feed.
>> Trixie can't see you. Return her sight
at once. You are adapting. A newborn
vampire senses are blurred and every
pony will appear as little more than
shadow. You won't be able to distinguish
between strangers and friends. The first
few hours are the most cruel. Until
midnight, you will feel insatiable with
a mindless drive to drink pony blood.
And also you have the limited power to
rewind time at your leisure.
Before you attempt to do that again, I
should inform you that your rewind
powers don't work on the vampire that
turned you.
Hey, Trixie. I know we never spoke a
single word to each other our entire
lives, but can you spot me $3 to order a
pepperoni pizza?
Holy [__]
>> Fluttershy, what's wrong?
>> Open your eyes, [__] Trixie is trying
to smash.
Lesbian, lesbian, lesbian.
>> It seems your friend has been bitten by
a vampire.
>> Oh, Drat. And we were just about to head
into town to get my free taco cart, too.
But I suppose that will have to wait for
another time. Pinkie Pie, fetch some
rope so we can tie her to a tree. I
would do it myself, but I don't want to
break my $12 faux amethyst nails. This
is deeply inconvenient. Should we tell
Twilight that Trixie is a monster?
>> No, Twilight is a [__] Also, Twilight
has the nose of a wolf now, and Trixie
is really stinky. She's already
suffering enough.
>> Speaking of stinky, I just crapped my
pants. We'll talk about what to do with
her later after I wipe my congealed [__]
and have my beauty rest.
>> I cannot believe you ate my homework.
I graded it for fun when you were
asleep. It would have been an F anyway.
I am undergoing a violent werewolf
transition and you left it on the floor.
But if you wait 3 hours, it will pass
through my body thanks to the miracle
that is biology. Anyway, I found this
book on the complete history of this
town. Did you know it's illegal to sell
tacos here? That can't be. How can
Rarity inherit a taco stand if taco
carts are illegal? And that's not even
the weirdest part. The inheritance makes
no sense either. The taco cart was never
owned by Rarity's family. Something
strange is going on here. Flawless, even
more so than werewolves and vampires.
And it has to do with tacos. You and I
are going to get to the bottom of this.
>> Damn, Fluttershy sure got some big butt
cheeks.
Hey, Fluttershy. Are you awake?
>> Yeah, it's hard to sleep on this extra
for mattress with this kind of booty.
>> Can you change my diaper?
>> Sorry, baby cakes, but that feels like
something you should handle yourself.
>> But I can't see back there.
>> If assistance is required. I shall
bravely volunteer.
>> Rarity, go back to your room. We
specifically got our own because we hate
you.
>> Yeah, I want Fluttershy to do it.
>> If you keep asking, I'm going to tell
your parents.
Oh, Pinkie Pie, I'm so sorry for yelling
at you, baby girl.
>> It's okay. You can make it up to me by
going with me into town to steal the
taco cart before Rarity gets it.
>> But it belongs to Rarity.
>> Fluttershy, I didn't want to say this
because it's embarrassing, but but
Rarity hits me.
>> Oh, baby, I didn't know. Okay, let's go
teach that horror lesson.
>> It's too high. Give me a boost so I can
climb over and then I'll pull you up.
>> Pinkie Pie, where did you go?
>> Huh? Stupid. Did you really think I
would help you?
>> You used me. You just want that taco
cart for yourself.
>> Fluttershy, I heard a branch break. That
wasn't you, was it?
>> No, I'm on the other side of the fence.
>> Fluttershy, I think Trixie broke free.
Help me. Haha, that's right. This is
what you deserve. Run for your pathetic
little life.
Who's there? The great and powerful
Trixie demands you make your presence
known.
Hey, check it. The moon's turning all
red.
Trixie,
shouldn't you be in the bedroom?
She's been bit.
Trixie, wait. Stop it. It's It's me.
Try. Trixie can't control herself.
>> You You've been bit. Okay. Uh, you can
drink a little.
>> I can't. If I start, I won't be able to
stop.
>> I read about vamporization. The first
hours are the worst, right? You need to
feed. If you feed only from me, albeit
in a controlled manner, you won't get
the urge to go on the attack.
Hey, where is Pinkie Pie? It is highly
unusual for that girl to miss breakfast
because she's fat.
>> Pinkie Pie is dead.
>> I'm sorry. What?
>> She attempted to steal my taco cart last
night.
>> I failed to see how that results in the
death of the most iconic My Little Pony
character ever. Apparently, she was
killed by a vampire, but Trixie swears
it was not her.
>> We've always had a lively night life. I
see. This town is evil, and it is
holding many dark secrets, even in this
very room.
>> What are you saying, darling?
>> I'm saying, Rarity, that you aren't
being entirely truthful with us, and I
will get to the very bottom of whatever
it is you are plotting here. Flawless,
let me ride you like a horsey. I don't
want to sit in this room of monsters and
liars anymore.
How are you feeling, Twilight? I'm fine.
We'll stop by the 7-Eleven and I'll get
some Alka-Seltzer on the way back.
>> Celestia's prized pupil, Twilight
Sparkle. You're here for answers about
that old mansion there at top that hill,
aren't you,
>> Mr. Mayor? Whatever information you can
provide would be extremely helpful.
Well, what is there to say? Everyone
knows the story hundreds of years ago.
An old orphanage used to be situated
there, operating for several centuries
before abruptly shutting down after a
fire.
>> And what about the mayor who lives
there, the one who takes care of the
library? As far as records show, the
building has been vacant since its
closure, Miss Sparkle. Whatever happens
at that mansion should be of no concern
to you.
>> You're talking about that mansion like
it's the Abstain Island. Okay, let's
change the topic to something simpler.
What about the taco cart? Why is it
going to Rarity?
>> I don't know. As I recall, the original
owner of that taco cart died
approximately 10 years ago and it's been
collecting dust since. But witnesses say
moments before his demise that he was
confronted by a couple of teenage girls.
But 3 months ago, the legislation
changed and street vendors were
permitted to start selling tacos.
>> Wait here, Twilight. I'm going to use my
command over mirrors to journey to the
past.
Ow.
This is exactly 10 years in the past.
Now I can figure out the truth. Hey,
there's the taco cart.
Is that Rarity and my mom as little
Phillies? They're so cute.
>> Good afternoon, darling. We're here to
discuss acquisition.
>> Hey, kiddos. You're just in time for the
first taco of the day. have one on me
free of charge.
>> Type [__] But nah, mister. We want the
taco cart and we are prepared to offer
you a generous sum of $12.
>> It's all the money in our piggy banks.
You would be wise to accept our offer.
>> A shucks. Sorry, kids. It ain't for
sale.
>> I'm afraid this has become an unpleasant
situation for you, darling. Trixie, take
the money.
>> Hey, let go.
>> No, you let go of the silly and
rambunctious Trixie's money. It's not
yours. Help some pony. Help me.
>> Did you just try to shoot me?
>> The gun jammed. Let's make like hockey
sticks and get the puck out of here.
Oh, Trixie, I cannot believe you have
done this.
What have you discovered? You ain't
going to believe this [__] Trixie and
Rarity killed the original taco stand
owner for his cart when he refused to
sell. And they've returned to claim it
now that the laws have changed. Why
wouldn't I believe it? That sounds
exactly like something they would do.
Let's go.
>> I'm afraid you two aren't going
anywhere. You see, it's been a while
since I had fresh meat.
Don't you dare step up on me.
Thank you all for coming. A rarity, I
see you headed into town to receive your
taco cart. Type [__] type [__] That is
extremely topical to what we are about
to discuss.
>> You're welcome, [__] 10 years ago, the
original taco truck owner was killed and
Pinkie Pie was stabbed by a unicorn at
some point in the night for trying to
steal the taco cart.
>> Yes, tragic. We've established this.
Wherever are you going with this,
Twilight?
>> Flawless jumped back in time. She saw
you and Trixie confront the taco cart
owner and murder him.
>> That don't prove jack [__]
>> Trixie, is there anything else you've
been lying to us about?
>> Trixie was the one who peed in the
Dashcon ball pit.
Applejack.
>> That's Fluttershy.
>> Fluttershy? I should have known.
>> That's right. 10 years ago, I followed
Rarity and Trixie when they tried to mug
him,
but they failed. 30 minutes later, I
walked up and killed him with a big ass
watermelon.
I then located the ownership papers that
were located on the taco card next to
the shredded cheese and ground beef. And
I changed the name to Rarity. But why
me? Because I knew taco selling would
eventually be legalized. And when that
day came, the taco cart would go to you,
Rarity. That way, all of the suspicions
would fall on you would get arrested.
Then in the middle of the night, I would
go to your house and steal the taco
cart. You followed Rarity across cities,
waited for law reform, and committed
murder, forged documents, and planned a
delayed property theft. And you've been
planning all this for 10 years. anything
to secure a financial future.
>> I hate to break it to you, Fluttershy,
but I don't think you're securing
anything with one taco cart. Do you even
know how to make tacos?
>> No. That's why when I actually got a T,
I was going to hire a Mexican.
>> So then you would have to split the
money in half. How the hell did you
expect to make any money?
She's got an idea. Flawless. No, but
living with you isn't cheap. You have
fancy tastes. Every time we get hot dogs
at the gas station, you add chili and
cheese. That's a 50 cent add-on.
>> Oh my god, she killed Rarity.
>> That's Pinky.
>> Pinkie Pie is going to fly in through
that window in a few seconds. With these
new powers, I can change things before
they happen.
I'm sorry you weren't able to find the
information you need in our library.
I'll contact you should anything turn
up. I had a talk with the mayor. Their
place isn't supposed to be any residents
here since the fire hundreds of years
ago. Who are you?
>> What is this? I'm showing you who I am.
>> Take a look at this graph.
I can't quite see it clearly.
>> This area here between the dura matter
and the surface of the brain is where
blood has been slowly collecting. I'm
afraid you have what's called a chronic
subdural hematoma. There's a slow bleed
between your brain and skull. It seems
to have been building over time.
>> That sounds serious.
>> It is. It's likely what's contributing
to your vision loss and cognitive
decline. The pressure is affecting
critical areas of your brain. For
someone your age, this kind of condition
isn't unheard of. But the combination of
symptoms, it complicates things.
>> So, what do I do?
>> There's no time to lose. I'll admit you
tonight, and we'll prep you for surgery
tomorrow morning overseas. I'll prepare
the arrangements.
I love you. I've always loved you.
You'll never know what my heart went
through being taken away from you.
I want you to know that every second we
had together, those were the most
precious moments of my life.
That was the very last time I saw her
alive.
Years later, I ended crashing my
motorbike in the pouring rain, breaking
multiple bones in my body. I lied there
completely ignored as cars drove by, not
even thinking for a second to come to my
aid. I was buried in the cemetery next
to the old orphanage I was raised.
My body was exumed by a vampire who was
planning on a late night meal. He didn't
expect me to fight back when the venom
entered my body and ended up becoming
the meal instead. I didn't realize how
much time had passed until I returned to
the orphanage, only to learn that it had
been shut down for hundreds of year. I
was forgotten in time. So, I burned it
to the ground. The mansion was built
directly on top of my home's ashes.
>> Why did you turn Trixie?
>> It's within a vampire to desire blood. I
would have fed on anyone you had. I was
given the chance. It's clear to me that
girl is personally precious to you. And
for that, I do apologize for turning
her. You have given me much to consider,
Twilight Sparkle. In return, I will
share with you the wisdom of undoing a
night creature's metamorphosis.
But you must act immediately if you
don't want to stay that way forever. In
the end, Sky Wishes was of no help. So,
we checked on Google instead. I was
finally able to figure out how to undo
my werewolf transformation. And turns
out it can only be done in one place,
the My Little Pony version of Germany
during a special holiday where the
ponies cloak themselves in red to
celebrate the night cryptids were
expelled from the land. The moon must be
at its peak and a werewolf has to drink
the warm coagulated booty cheek sweat of
a pink pony. The way to undo
vampurification is much more preferable
where they must drink 18 cups of piss.
Rarity and Fluttershy went home to
Ponyville to sell tacos and Pinky went
to buy a Jeep at the local car
dealership because they had one on sale.
Hey,
>> the great and powerful Trixie can go a
few hours without feeding Sparkle. Go to
sleep.
>> It's not that. There's something I want
to ask.
>> What is it?
>> That story Sky Wishes told. If you were
to bite someone who had died,
theoretically, you could still turn
them.
>> Seems so.
>> What about your dad? Trixie killed him.
He was abusive and he hurt Trixiey's
mother and sister. So Trixie feels no
reason to bring him back.
>> That's fair, I suppose. Then how about
your mom?
>> Trixie considered it, but decided
against it because this world was not
kind to her. Trixie would be dragging
her back into the same world that killed
her in the first place. She suffered
enough here. You've changed. Obviously,
Trixie drinks blood now.
>> That's not what I mean. You have the
power to change fate, but you just let
it be.
>> Because I married you. The day we got
married, I realized there wasn't
anything left to chase. I don't need to
resurrect the past because I get to wake
up next to the most brilliant, stubborn,
and beautiful mare in the world. Even
though you're a vampire and I'm a
werewolf and we're taking a train across
a frozen continent.
>> Well, you've always been kind of a
[__]
>> And you've always had one hell of a
bite.
God damn, these [__] really know how
to party.
>> Yeah, you just know those guys are gay
as [__]
Questo se.
>> Oh my god, vampire hunting is so fun.
It's like we get to murder people but
legally.
>> Yeah, we really should have done this
ages ago.
>> What?
A train just pulled up. Is that Twilight
and Trixie?
>> Hey, is it just me or do Trixiey's eyes
look redder to you?
>> It's probably just the glare of the
moon.
>> Hey, what are you doing, Pooky? I'm
using the vampire hunting legislation to
shoot Twilight Sparkle in the head. Get
your arm out of the way. Are you still
going on about the marshmallow incident?
Duh, [__] Move.
You still never told me about that.
>> It's not something I love to talk about.
>> Starlight,
I'm not going to let you shoot my
stepsister in the head without an
explanation.
>> Mommy, daddy, look what I found.
>> Honey, Starlight disembowled the school
bus driver
>> again. I'll start another bath.
Mama, where are my marshmallows?
For my show and tell, I wanted to show
off my cooking expertise by making
sugarcoated marshmallows. I made these
myself. Princess Celestia can I pass
them around.
>> Only if I get one, too. I love
marshmallows almost as much as the Holy
Bible. Hallelujah. Praise Jesus.
>> Every pony gets one. And yes, even you,
Sparkle, my rival.
>> Why are they shaped like meatballs?
That's so yucky. Haven't you made
marshmallows before?
>> They're homemade, so they're not going
to look exactly like the ones you buy
from Walmart.
>> You mean to tell me you touched these
with your hooves? The same ones you used
to walk around on in the dirt and horse
[__] That's gross. Well, no one is
forcing you to eat it. Give it to me so
I can put it on my own desk. Hey, Pinkie
Pie, here's a quarter. I'm going to take
a fat crap. Watch my marshmallow so
Twilight doesn't do anything to it.
Hey, Pinky, I'll trade you a penny for
that quarter if you give me the
marshmallow.
>> What are you doing with that?
>> I'm rolling the marshmallow around in
laxative powder. This stuff will make
that stupid Philly [__] herself all day
long.
>> Dang, Sparkle, you are such a baddie.
Remind me never to get on your bad side.
She's coming back quickly. Put it back
on the desk. We have one.
>> Hey, Twilight. I just wanted to say,
well, maybe we got off on the wrong hoof
today. You You think so?
>> Yeah. And honestly, you're like my
friend and the only one who gets me. So,
thanks for watching my marshmallow with
Pinkie Pie.
>> Well, [__] It ain't nothing at all,
[__] Put that [__] in your mouth.
Yo, is it good, [__] Yeah, just uh
give me a second. Princess Celestia, can
I go take a dump?
>> No. Starlight, you just went put your
hoof down.
>> But this time it's different. I really
need to poopy.
>> No.
>> Hey yo, what the [__]
Oh no.
That was you. But Ponyville was thrust
into an endless winter as the sun was
blotted out for six months until
Celestia finally managed to clear it.
Every pony thought we were under nuclear
attack by terrorists. That's just what
the government said to ease the tension.
So they wouldn't realize they were
living next door to the real danger. Me.
Only our classmates know what really
happened on that day. And they still
follow me on pony socials to bully me
and call me things like [__] And
that [__] Twilight never got in any
trouble for tampering with your
marshmallow. I can't believe she did
that to you.
>> Princess Celestia already had eyes on
her and was already planning on making
her her next student. So if I told on
her, I would have probably went to jail.
>> Oh, Starlight, come on. Let's go outside
and hunt some more vampires. That'll
cheer you up.
>> Mary, stop. That's not a vampire. That
is literally some random guy.
Mary, stop it. But vampires drink blood.
He's covered in blood.
>> Because you're literally beating the
crap out of him.
>> Oh, my bad.
>> And for the love of God, stop killing
the vampires. They're worth way more
alive.
>> I'm sorry. I don't have magic to end
duels without bloodshed like you do.
>> Whatever. You're just dead. Wait. Go
back to the apartment and make me a
below knee and cheese sandwich.
>> What did you just say?
>> Hey. Hey. I didn't mean it like that.
Cutie Pop. Take that thing off. Mama
just want a sandwich.
>> Hey, quick question. Can I have that
vampire?
>> No. Piss off.
>> Dude, come on. Me and my gay lover
Thorax are struggling out in this [__]
Like, we came here to make money, but we
haven't caught a single vampire because
they're like so sexy that I just keep
having sex with them and sucking their
nuts.
Thorax is giving me the silent treatment
now because we're broke as [__] and he
found out I've been sleeping around with
these sexy gay vampires and [__]
>> Isn't that the changeling I decapitated
months ago?
>> Thorax, the ponies want to talk to you.
You know, when we got back to Ponyville,
I was going to take you to Denny's and
treat you to a Grand Slam meal, but I'm
thinking I won't do that. I'll just buy
two Grand Slams for myself.
>> Every pony run, a vampire swarm is
coming right towards us. T-Rex, don't
let them surround you or you're
finished.
>> Why are they only targeting me? Either
they're homophobic or my massive butt
cheeks clapping together are triggering
their bat sonar abilities. Get away from
me, you [__] freaks. I didn't do
anything to you. Thorax, help me.
>> This is so weird. Every pony looks like
baby Belell cheese wheels.
>> Twilight.
>> Oh, Twilight, why did you do that?
>> Oh gosh. I'm sorry. I didn't realize it
was you, Marionette.
>> A [__] Twilight, there's some pony
spying on you from behind the trash
cans.
>> Oh, that's just Starlight Glimmer. She
does that kind of thing a lot because
she's jealous of me. What is Marionette
doing now?
>> Sisters of Russia, you have been
oppressed by the patriarchy for far too
long. Join me and together we can purge
the world of the dick havvers.
What the actual buck are you doing right
now? Preaching the good word of
feminism.
Cool. Cool. In case you forgot, we are
vampire hunting. And tonight is the one
night of the year where every
bloodrinking creature within a thousand
miles is feeling festive. Don't stand
out by getting on top of a cardboard box
and advertising yourself like a premium
snack in this [__] Your face already
looks like one big strip of bacon.
>> I get your point.
>> What the hell is this? You got bit. I
know it looks bad. Twilight bit me. And
>> you're damn right. A werewolf bite. You
couldn't even have the audacity to get
bit by a vampire. At least then you'd be
worth something.
>> You're not going to turn me in for
money.
>> Darling baby, I'm just going to skin you
alive and turn you into a rug.
>> Oh, Starlight, I've waited so long to
hear you say those words. Please make
love to me.
Well, well, well, if it isn't Tara
Strong.
>> Spike, you're alive. But how?
>> Well, Spike, after 2 months, you're
finally being discharged from the
hospital. We're going to miss you.
>> Shut the hell up, you dumb broad.
>> Congratulations on being discharged from
the hospital, Spike. I've been waiting
behind Twilight Sparkle house for you to
come home for months.
>> Shut the hell up. I can't wait to see
the look on Twilight's face when she
sees that me, her best friend, has been
discharged from the hospital. That [__]
better make me my favorite dinner of
Salsbury steak with green beans and
mashed potatoes with gravy.
Oh, fist my butt sideways and spank my
ass cheeks. She ain't even in there.
Where did she go?
>> I think they're going to Italy to cure a
werewolf bite.
>> Twilight is a weird dog thing now. What
the hell did I miss?
>> I literally told you what happened. I
don't know how I could have made it any
clearer. What are you going to do now?
>> I don't know. Join a cult, probably.
>> Are you freaking stupid? You can't join
a cult. You're 2 ft tall. You'll be the
first one ritually sacrificed.
>> I mean it, Sparky. My life in Ponyville
is over. My only option now is to leave
the [__] behind and dedicate my life to
some ominous robewearing cryptic ass
organization. I don't go by Spike
anymore. Just High Priest, Supreme
Overlord of the Blood Moon. You are a
baby dragon.
>> I am a sex symbol.
>> You have never had sex.
>> How dare you say such a factual thing?
But unfortunately, your belief on
whether or not I get ass is not relevant
to my divine rulership.
>> Hold him still so I can snip off his
balls.
>> Ow! The [__] has a taser. Would a big
strong stallion give this little guy
some upsies and dress him in my
ceremonial robes?
What brings you here to the My Little
Pony version of Germany?
Sorry about that. Talking to the female
gender makes me want to puke. Anyway,
what brings you wenches to my domain? Do
you also wish to bask in the presence of
true greatness that is the unholy blood
moon? I want to punch you across a
football field so bad.
>> You are free to try, [__] but I would
advise against it because I have a gun.
>> Okay, hold on. Are you telling me you
run this place?
>> No, but I will after the blood moon
chooses me as its unholy vessel because
I am obviously half gnome, therefore a
crypted.
>> [__] You're not half gnome. You
just can't cope that you're short
because you got shitty ass genetics
similar to my mare pattern baldness. The
blood moon belongs to the creatures of
the night like the exalted and undying
Trixie.
>> I'd rather be short than bald and look
like a cancer patient like you.
>> High priest. There's a Jeep speeding up
the road.
>> What the hell is a Jeep?
>> A Jeep is a four-wheel driven vehicle.
>> So, a car? Why didn't you just say that?
>> Starlight, hurry. Throw one of your fart
bombs.
See, this is further proof that the
blood moon is here to save me.
>> Bro, out here thinking the blood moon
will grant him magic superiority because
his life sucks. Oh no, the poor dragon
in Cell can't get laid. Boo freaking
who?
>> The only way for us to know who the
blood moon truly favors is battle
through sacred combat.
>> Oh, I've been waiting for this.
>> I'm going to beat you up right now,
Twilight. I used to change your diapers
when you were a baby. Now I'm going to
kick your little ass.
Yeah, Twilight. Beat his ass. Hit him
again.
Twilight, the moon is at its peak. We
can undo the werewolf and
vampurification now. Remember what we
have to do. I have to drink 16 jugs of
piss. And you have to drink the booty
cheek sweat of a pink pony.
>> Oh, I'm going to enjoy this.
>> She ran over your Supreme Overlord. Take
her to the dungeons.
>> Oh, I'm going to enjoy this.
They locked themselves behind that door
with an abnormally large keyhole. How
will we save Rainbow Dash's best friend,
Pinky, now?
>> Move. I'm gay.
>> Take that, [__]
>> Dragons don't belong here.
>> Who the [__] is that? Get out of our
country.
>> Oh my god. Spike has been assassinated.
The moon is falling from the sky. Why is
it falling? It's part of the festival.
At the end of the night, Princess Luna
drops the moon on the town so the ponies
can rebuild it to represent death and
rebirth. We have to go now or else we'll
be crushed to death.
>> Twilight, help me.
>> No. This way, we'll use the train car
playing Russian trans music to escape.
Ah! Marionette, are you okay?
>> Don't worry about me. Just get in the
tram and go.
>> She's turning into a werewolf. We have
to leave her, Sparkle.
>> Oh my god, the werewolf bite is changing
her into a monster. And now her
stockings can't contain voluuptuous
pumpkin crushing.
>> The same thing didn't happen to me
because I'm already sexy.
Y'all run. I'll hold her back.
You know what I literally just realized?
>> What? We literally left Flawless in
Italy.
>> [__]
Oh, you crazy bastards. I haven't felt
this catered to since I discovered free
math games on the Google Play Store.
Not going to lie, watching moons fall
down from the sky, crushing thousands of
men. New favorite hobby. You're so cute
when you talk about war crimes. Stop
declaring war on half the species. I
don't consider men a species.
>> All right, you [__] I'm back for
revenge.
>> Spike, go home. We ain't doing this on
my birthday. Is that a rocket launcher?
Where did you get that? The dark web.
>> You can't buy militaryra weapons online.
>> You can on the dark web.
>> Spike, run away. It's going to come back
down.
>> We are gathered here at the cemetery
located right behind the laser tag pizza
place combo. Not in mourning, but in
celebration. Since the day I was born,
this scaly little bastard has been my
lifelong rival. He was a cocky,
delusional, self-important, narcissistic
little [__] boy who thought he had main
character energy, and now he's dead as
[__] Now, I know some of you are
wondering, "But Sparky, don't you care
that you had to witness your best friend
die four times by now? Don't you feel
bad? Hell no. Why would I? I'm the main
protagonist of the hit franchise. My
Little Pony friendship is magic. Spike
was a loser who thought every pony loved
him. He thought he was going to have a
harum of [__] worshiping him. Not a
single [__] wants a dragon in a show
about ponies. That's why I selfidentify
as a pony. And that's a why I hired a
pony in Germany to take him out.
>> Preach it, little dragon baby.
>> But you know what? I got to hand it to
the little butt muncher. He gave me
something no other dragon ever could.
And what was that little dragon baby?
>> A free win. Never before have I caught a
more stray dub in my life. So rest in
piss spike, you little [__]
You were never my equal, but you were a
great punching bag.
What's wrong, Marionette? You've been
quiet the whole hunt. There were ponies
in the market talking about werewolves.
They said there that I'm dangerous
and it hurt your feelings because you
are a werewolf. I see how it is. Well,
it's not like they're entirely wrong.
That's exactly right. No one cares to
witness the ugly spectacle of a werewolf
miserably fumbling to imitate Pony. It's
revolting as it is pathetic. You appear
to understand just how feudal it is. The
harder you try to stay normal, the more
obvious it is that you are a faximile.
It is. I was waiting to see if you would
embrace the dog in you that I always
knew was there. Yet you appear satisfied
to instead act in my image. Why, I have
half a mind to throw you out of here. I
have no tolerance for cheap mimicry. I
do got that dog in me. Remember how I
nibbles at your hooves? And to top it
all off, you still can't capture
vampires without killing them. You can't
follow basic instructions. So, we're
returning to the basics. I'm sorry,
Bark. You're joking. Let me make
something very clear, Marionette. Before
you were metaphorically my [__] Now
you are literally a [__]
>> What? Shut up, [__]
See, that wasn't so hard. Well, I guess
it was for your fluffy butt because
you're bad at a lot of things except
throwing it back whenever I demand.
That's about the only thing you're good
at. Maybe there's hope for you after
all, little mut.
Hey, put on this blindfold right quick.
Okay, now what? Just keep facing the
wall. We're going to play a little game.
No peeking.
Why does it sound like you're loading a
shotgun? You're not planning on killing
me, are you?
>> I have no idea what you're talking
about.
>> I have supernaturally enhanced hearing.
>> Okay, first of all, werewolf fur prices
are extremely high right now. Do you
have any idea? Don't turn around. Do you
have any idea how financially
irresponsible it would be for me to not
at least evaluate the opportunity? You
cannot evaluate the opportunity of
murdering your mare friend. God, she
would make for such a nice rug, though.
I could step on her everyday. I mean, I
do regardless, but if she were a rug, I
wouldn't have to hear her complain about
it.
>> Starlight, you're thinking out loud.
>> Damn it. Well, it's not like I was going
to do it.
She's all about love for me. Only in my
phone once a week got me losing who I
used to be. But I love the way she loves
me for me once or twice. Couldn't say I
care at night. Got the bedroom dancing
right. Yeah. I love the way I love the
way she me.
She's a real bad for me. Only in my
phone once a week. Got me losing new I
used to be. But I love the way she loves
me for me once or twice. going to say I
can't
dancing right. Yeah. I love the way I
love the way shows me.